# Mario Quirós Luna

■ marioql.dev@gmail.com in LinkedIn Github Portfolio

I am a person with a great passion for technology. I have 6 months of supervised internship experience and also more than 3 years working on personal projects to gain skills in various technologies. I am characterized by being organized, responsible, a team leader, and positive. As a professional, I define myself as an autonomous, self-taught, analytical, and solution-oriented person, with the ability to work in a team and a great willingness to face new challenges and projects.

### Education

03/2017 - 12/2023 Costa Rica Universidad de Costa Rica, Computer Science

## Skills

- Flutter, ReactNative
- React, Angular, .NET, Node
- SQLServer, MySQL, Mongo

- Kotlin, Java
- · Javascript, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap
- Git, GitHub

# **Professional Experience**

08/2023 - present Costa Rica

## FullStack Developer, Nearlinx ☑

Development of a highly functional and customized ERP platform for comprehensive resource management within the company.

- ✓ Design and development of a platform tailored to the company's needs.
- Recording of employee hours and payments.
- Efficiency in project billing.
- ✓ Visual reports through dashboards.
- Financial reports.
- SCRUMBAN work methodology.
- ✓ Remote mode.
  - .Net, Entity Framework, MVC, Bootstrap, Figma, Git, Gitflow, SCRUMBAN

03/2020 - present Costa Rica

### FullStack Developer, Personal Projects

With more than 25 personal projects, I have demonstrated my ability to continuously learn and apply my knowledge through web and mobile applications. You can check my GitHub for documentation on these projects.

- Flutter, ReactNative, React, .NET, Angular, SASS, Kotlin, Java, NodeJS.

03/2023 - 07/2023 Costa Rica

#### FullStack Developer, Universidad de Costa Rica

As a part of a 5-person development team, I actively participated in an project to create a hotel reservation website. We followed an agile SCRUM methodology and worked based on a prototype provided by the client.

- Angular, .Net, SQL, Git, SCRUM

07/2022 - 12/2022Costa Rica

#### BackEnd Developer,

Universidad de Costa Rica y Organismo de Investigación Judicial (OIJ)

✓ Development of a control management system for offices, users, roles, permissions, and periods.

✓ Implementation of a user interface that allowed the visualization of control statuses through graphics.

Recording and tracking of user activity and system errors.

✓ Enablement of file (PDF) uploads for control evidence.

✓ Utilization of a multi-layer infrastructure architecture to ensure system scalability and performance.

- .NET, EntityFramework, SQL, Git.

## Certificates

Flutter and Dart

Udemy

**Mobile App Development ☑** 

Google Activate

LinkedIn

.Net ☑ LinkedIn

AWS Cloud fundamentals

Udemy

Real Android App with Kotlin

Udemy

Advanced Javascript

LinkedIn

**Android Development** 2

LinkedIn

Testing/QA ☑ LinkedIn

Introduction to FrontEnd

byMeta

Coursera

Advanced Angular

LinkedIn

ReactNative

LinkedIn

SCRUM Fundamentals 2

**SCRUMstudy** 

# Awards

05/2023

Cybersecurity Policy Competitor, Cyber4Dev ☑

International representation in the Dominican Republic, with the CSC Costa Rica team, University of Costa Rica.

01/2023 - 03/2023

Community Service

FrontEnd Web Development Professor, Universidad de Costa Rica

· HTML, CSS, Javascript

01/2023 - 03/2023

Costa Rica

Costa Rica

BackEnd Web Development Professor, Universidad de Costa Rica

• C#, .NET, POO, EntityFramework, SQL

# Languages

Spanish **English** Native B1